{
    "questions": [
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 1,
            "question": "\"When developing a backlink strategy, what approach would be most beneficial?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Guest post the article to as many sites as possible\"",
            "choices": [
                "Guest post the article to as many sites as possible",
                "Create an infographics and share it with relevant bloggers",
                "Create diverse and unnatural links",
                "Distribute links in comment sections of websites"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 2,
            "question": "\"What is a key reason the URL `domain.com/apparel/jackets` is preferable to the URL `domain.com/p=141`?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"It is readable to a human\"",
            "choices": [
                "It is longer",
                "It is not preferable",
                "It uses structured markup",
                "It is readable to a human"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 3,
            "question": "\"Which HTTP response status code would indicate a page has been moved permanently?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"301\"",
            "choices": [
                "410",
                "302",
                "200",
                "301"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 4,
            "question": "\"You notice a website is serving HTML to a Search Engine than to a human user. What is this an example of?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Cloaking\"",
            "choices": [
                "Spam injection",
                "Cloaking",
                "Sneaky Redirect",
                "Splicing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 5,
            "question": "\"What would significantly improve Google&#39;s ability to a non-YouTube video in its Search Results?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Add Schema.org VideoObject\"",
            "choices": [
                "Provide a 150 x 80 pixel thumbnail image",
                "Add Schema.org VideoObject",
                "Convert .mp4 videos to .mov",
                "Embed video objects with JavaScript conditionals"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 6,
            "question": "\"Google primarily determines indexing and ranking by crawling which version of a page?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Responsive version\"",
            "choices": [
                "Responsive version",
                "Submitted version",
                "Mobile version",
                "Desktop version"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 7,
            "question": "\"You want to identify which US state has the most search interest for a particular keyword. What tool would help you determine this?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Google Trends\"",
            "choices": [
                "Google Analytics",
                "Google Keyword Planner",
                "Google Search Console",
                "Google Trends"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 8,
            "question": "\"You want to block crawlers from accessing your entire website. What robots.txt entry would you use?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\":\"",
            "choices": [
                ":",
                "```markdown\nUser-agent: Allbots\nDisallow: \\*\n```",
                ":",
                "```markdown\nUser-agent: /\nDisallow: \\*\n```",
                ":",
                "```markdown\nUser-agent: /\nDisallow:\n```",
                ":",
                "```markdown\nUser-agent: \\*\nDisallow: /\n```"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 9,
            "question": "\"Which result is most likely if you use an interstitial pop-up that requires a user to take action before you load the content of the page?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"The pop-up will be indexed instead of the desired body content\"",
            "choices": [
                "Both the pop-up and the content of the page will be indexed",
                "The pop-up will be indexed instead of the desired body content",
                "An interstitial pop-up is treated the same as a soft 404",
                "The pop-up will be ignored, and the content of the page will be indexed correctly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 10,
            "question": "\"You notice a particular product in an e-commerce storefront is no longer indexed, despite no technical issues. What is a likely reason for this?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"No title or meta description tags were provided\"",
            "choices": [
                "No title or meta description tags were provided",
                "The Keywords is too competitive",
                "Robots.txt is configured to allow access",
                "The product is out of stock"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 11,
            "question": "\"All byline dates for articles are suddenly no longer visible on a `website&#39;s` listing within Google Search. Assuming no changes have been made to the site programming or content, what is the most likely cause?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site\"",
            "choices": [
                "The site has been delisted from Google Search",
                "A Google News sitemap was not provided within 30 days of setting up a publisher center account",
                "The site kept updating the dates to make the content appear fres, without changing",
                "The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 12,
            "question": "\"Which approach is not advisable to Geo-targeting your website?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"using URL parameters\"",
            "choices": [
                "Using a gTLD with subdomain",
                "using URL parameters",
                "Using a ccTLD",
                "Using a gTLD with a subdirectory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 13,
            "question": "\"You have been asked to help a big e-commerce brand optimize their website for search engines. They currently have thousands of products listed on their website. What is your most appropriate first step?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Work on compressing image files\"",
            "choices": [
                "Recommend that they add more products",
                "Work on compressing image files",
                "302 redirect all product pages to URL that contains target keywords",
                "Register the business with a Google My Business account."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 14,
            "question": "\"What Does The Term &quot;Sandbox&quot; Mean In SEO?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"This Is Where Sites Are Kept Till They Get Mature Enough To Be Included In The Top Rankings For A Particular Keyword\"",
            "choices": [
                "The Box With Paid Ads That Appear When You Perform A Search.",
                "This Is Where Sites Are Kept Till They Get Mature Enough To Be Included In The Top Rankings For A Particular Keyword",
                "A Special Category Of Sites That Are Listed In Kid-safe Searches",
                "The First 10 Search Results For A Particular Keyword."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 15,
            "question": "\"What Is Anchor Text?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"It Is The Visible Text That Is Hyper Linked To Another Page\"",
            "choices": [
                "It Is The Main Body Of Text On A Particular Web Page",
                "It Is The Text Within The Left Or Top Panel Of A Web Page",
                "It Is The Visible Text That Is Hyper Linked To Another Page",
                "It Is The Most Prominent Text On The Page That The Search Engines Use To Assign A Title To The Page"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 16,
            "question": "\"Which Google search query should be used to return only PDF documents that reference Microsoft?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Microsoft filetype:pdf\"",
            "choices": [
                "Microsoft + .pdf",
                "\"Microsoft\" + \"pdf\"",
                "Microsoft AND \"pdf\"",
                "Microsoft filetype:pdf"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 17,
            "question": "\"Which link is not crawlable?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`<a onclick=\"newwin('domain.com')\">`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`<a href=\"http://domain.com\">`",
                "`<a onclick=\"newwin('domain.com')\">`",
                "`<a href=\"http://domain.com\" class=\"blue\">`",
                "`<a href=\"../category-2/page\">`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 18,
            "question": "\"Which choice represents the best header structure?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\":\"",
            "choices": [
                ":",
                "```markdown\nH1: How to Bak Bagels\nH2: Ingredients\nH3: Dry Ingredients\nH4: Wet Ingredients\nH2: Instructions\nH6: Reviews\n```",
                ":",
                "```markdown\nH1: How to Bak Bagels\nH1: Ingredients\nH1: Dry Ingredients\nH1: Wet Ingredients\nH1: Instructions\nH2: Reviews\n```",
                ":",
                "```markdown\nH1: How to Bak Bagels\nH2: Ingredients\nH3: Dry Ingredients\nH3: Wet Ingredients\nH2: Instructions\nH2: Reviews\n```",
                ":",
                "```markdown\nH1: How to Bak Bagels\nH2: Ingredients\nH4: Dry Ingredients\nH5: Wet Ingredients\nH6: Instructions\nH1: Reviews\n```"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 19,
            "question": "\"All byline dates articles are suddenly no longer visible on a website's listing within Google Search. Assuming no changes have been made to the site programming or content, what is the most likely cause?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"The site kept updating the date to make the content appear fresh, without changing the content.\"",
            "choices": [
                "The site has been delisted from Google Search",
                "The site kept updating the date to make the content appear fresh, without changing the content.",
                "The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site.",
                "A Google New sitemap was not provided within 30 days of setting up a Publisher Center account"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 20,
            "question": "\"What is an example of a Google search result that can be found in position zero?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"featured snippet\"",
            "choices": [
                "Google Ads result",
                "featured snippet",
                "related searches",
                "autocomplete"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 21,
            "question": "\"When creating accessible video content, what should you consider including?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"transcript\"",
            "choices": [
                "transcript",
                "thumbnail",
                "Flash Player",
                "event tracking"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 22,
            "question": "\"You are optimizing a website that sells supplies for banking donuts. Which approach is most appropriate to drive more organic traffic?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Create a new blog with high-quality donut recipes\"",
            "choices": [
                "Buy donutbakingsupplies.com and 301 redirect to your website",
                "Add the keyword \"donut supplies\" to every page.",
                "Create a new blog with high-quality donut recipes",
                "Join a link farm to rapidly build inbounnd links."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 23,
            "question": "\"Why is it important to be mindful of outbound follow links?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Your site's reputation is tied to the sites you link to.\"",
            "choices": [
                "There is a limit to how many links you can create.",
                "all of these answers",
                "Any follow links reduce your PageRank by 1.",
                "Your site's reputation is tied to the sites you link to."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 24,
            "question": "\"Which statement is true about JSON-LD?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"It is Google's preferred structured data format.\"",
            "choices": [
                "It has no relation to JSON.",
                "It is the only structured data format available.",
                "It is considered the most complicated approach to adding structured data.",
                "It is Google's preferred structured data format."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 25,
            "question": "\"What is a key reason why duplicate content might cause an issue with ranking?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"It makes it difficult for a search engine to determine the original and authoritative content source.\"",
            "choices": [
                "It creates an inability to use canonical URLs, which dramatically reduces crawl effectiveness,",
                "It requires using a 302 redirect, which dilutes PageRank.",
                "It triggers an immediate manual action penalty, which delists an entire domain until the duplicate content is removed.",
                "It makes it difficult for a search engine to determine the original and authoritative content source."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 26,
            "question": "\"What attribute would you use to describe the content of an image?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"alt\"",
            "choices": [
                "tabindex",
                "longdesc",
                "src",
                "alt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 27,
            "question": "\"You are researching keywords for a client and creating list for an optimization plan. Which is _not_ a recommended method of creating keyword lists?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"focusing on only high-volume, high-popularity words\"",
            "choices": [
                "synonyms and related words",
                "queries about benefits, features, problems",
                "how-to and question-based queries",
                "focusing on only high-volume, high-popularity words"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 28,
            "question": "\"You want to get a rough idea of how many searches per month a particular search term gets. Which tool do you use?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Google Keyword Planner\"",
            "choices": [
                "Google Keyword Planner",
                "Google Tag Manager",
                "Google Search Console",
                "Google Suggest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 29,
            "question": "\"Changing the title tag and/or meta description will have a measurable impact on your \\_.\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"CTR\"",
            "choices": [
                "RSS",
                "CTR",
                "PPC",
                "LSI"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 30,
            "question": "\"How do keywords change as people progress through the buying cycle?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"They move from simple to more complex as searchers gather more information and then refine their choices.\"",
            "choices": [
                "They move from simple to more complex as searchers gather more information and then refine their choices.",
                "The stay simple, as searchers try to use as few words as possible.",
                "The keywords do not change much at all.",
                "They move from complex to simple, as searchers find answers to their questions."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 31,
            "question": "\"Which technique is an example of black hat SEO?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"cloaking\"",
            "choices": [
                "cloaking",
                "keyword research",
                "useful content",
                "on-page optimization"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 32,
            "question": "\"A local accountant wants to start attracting more business directly from Google organic search. What is the best piece of advice to give to her?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Register her business with a Google Business Profile account.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Use the pharse \"local accountant\" as a keyword to focus her website on.",
                "Focus on short-tail keywords.",
                "Register her business with a Google Business Profile account.",
                "Leave a link to her website in the blog comments of popular accounting websites."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 33,
            "question": "\"What is the anchor text in this code sample?\"",
            "body": "`<a href=\"catalog/gloves.html\">Blue Gloves</a>`",
            "answer": "\"Blue Gloves\"",
            "choices": [
                "Blue Gloves",
                "href",
                "catalog/",
                "gloves.html"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 34,
            "question": "\"**\\_** analysis allows you to review requests made to your web server to identify insights such as how ofter a crawler arrives, what pages have 404 errors, and most crawled pages\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Log file\"",
            "choices": [
                "Log file",
                "HTTP/2",
                "Cron job",
                "Resource packet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 35,
            "question": "\"Which page title references content that is evergreen\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"How to Reheat Pizza\"",
            "choices": [
                "Mega List of Teams Going to the Olympics",
                "Complete Coverage of Microsoft's Latest Announcement",
                "The Future of SEO in 2020",
                "How to Reheat Pizza"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 36,
            "question": "\"You load a page and start reading an article, and suddenly the content on the page moves. What metric is used to quantify this impact on user experience?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS)\"",
            "choices": [
                "First Meaningful Paint (FMP)",
                "Recalculated Style Timing (RST)",
                "Latent Loading Signal (LLS)",
                "Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 37,
            "question": "\"What is this code is an example of?\"",
            "body": "```<script type=\"application/ld+json\">\n{\n   \"@context\": \"https://schema.org\",\n   \"@type\": \"Organization\",\n   \"url\": \"http://www.domain.com\",\n   \"name\": \"Bradley Corp.\",\n   \"contactPoint\": {\n      \"@type\": \"ContactPoint\",\n      \"telephone\": \"+1-555-555-5555\",\n      \"contactType\": \"Customer service\"\n    }\n}\n</script>\n```",
            "answer": "\"structured data\"",
            "choices": [
                "meta tag",
                "HTTP response",
                "XML sitemap",
                "structured data"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 38,
            "question": "\"Which search query would be most difficult to determine search intent?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Microsoft Office 365\"",
            "choices": [
                "XBox live coupon",
                "Microsoft Office 365",
                "LinkedIn login",
                "LAX airport directions"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 39,
            "question": "\"When you conduct a search, what are the bolded words within the search listing description?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"keywords that match the search query\"",
            "choices": [
                "suggested search terms",
                "related search queries",
                "keywords that match the search query",
                "words with a `<b>` tag assigned in their meta description"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 40,
            "question": "\"Which acronym is used to describe the page a user sees after submitting a search?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"SERP (Search Engine Results Page)\"",
            "choices": [
                "SERP (Search Engine Results Page)",
                "INDX",
                "PARS",
                "SEM"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 41,
            "question": "\"Which statement is true regarding the use of social signals, such as LinkedIn shares, by Google in its ranking algorithm?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Social signals are used to determine topic authority\"",
            "choices": [
                "Google does not use social signals to determine rank",
                "Social signals are identical to backlinks",
                "Social signals are used to determine topic authority",
                "Social signals provide a benefit only if they have structured data markup"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 42,
            "question": "\"A user clicks an internal link resulting in this redirect chain: `http://domain.com -> https://domain.com -> https://domain.com/`. In this example, what is being consumed unnecessarily?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"redirect allotment\"",
            "choices": [
                "redirect allotment",
                "crawl budget",
                "velocity scale",
                "domain authority"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 43,
            "question": "\"You are planning for the development of an e-commerce website. Which approach will be more beneficial for rankings?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Optimize the front page of your website to drive traffic from all category search terms.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Optimize the front page of your website to drive traffic from all category search terms.",
                "Optimize product category pages to drive traffic from individual category search terms.",
                "Optimize all pages on the site for all category search terms.",
                "Optimize product pages to drive traffic from individual category search terms."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 44,
            "question": "\"What is the relationship of click depth to PageRank?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"The deeper the click depth, the lower the PageRank\"",
            "choices": [
                "The deeper the click depth, the lower the PageRank",
                "PageRank and click depth have no relation",
                "The deeper the click depth, the higher the PageRank",
                "Click depth and PageRank are equal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 45,
            "question": "\"What is a popular technique for writing content with the goal of having it appear in a features snippet?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Write the question in a headline tag, and then answer it below in a format that matches the snippet type.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Write the question in a headline tag, and then answer it below in a format that matches the snippet type.",
                "Use the features snippet schema and apply an object that matches the correct snippet type.",
                "Google manually generates featured snippets, so there is no special technique.",
                "Submit the content through Google Search Console, and tag it with the correct snippet type."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 46,
            "question": "\"What is a common best practice for handling search result pages on a blog's built-in site search?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Set site research results to no-index.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Set site research results to no-index.",
                "Do not use site search.",
                "Set site search to 404.",
                "Add a canonical from the search result page to the home page."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 47,
            "question": "\"What might help a search engine understand the difference between an article on a dog bark versus tree bark?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"semantic analysis\"",
            "choices": [
                "tertiary analysis",
                "ranked choice trees",
                "semantic analysis",
                "knowledge graphs"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 48,
            "question": "\"A webpage has this tag: `<title>Brad's Bagels: How to Bake a Bagel</title>`. However, the Google search result for this page displays this title: \\_Brad's Bagels: Baking Bagels in the Oven\\_. What is a likely explanation?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Google generated a new title using text on the page that more closely matched the search query.\"",
            "choices": [
                "The title tag was placed within the <HEAD> section of the webpage, but not before the meta content tags, so Google cannot identify the actual title.",
                "The page is using structured data to define an alternative title object, which allows the search engine to pick a preferable version.",
                "A breadcrumb navigation is in use, which overrides the title tag supplied in the HTML.",
                "Google generated a new title using text on the page that more closely matched the search query."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 49,
            "question": "\"What alt attribute should be assigned to an image of a decorative line being used to separate content\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"alt=\"\"\"",
            "choices": [
                "alt=\"\"",
                "alt=\"Thin black line being used to seperate two blocks of content\"",
                "alt=\"dec\"",
                "alt=\"thin-line\""
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 50,
            "question": "\"Your site serves identical content when you visit domain.com/page or domain.com/page?ref=123. What should you implement?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"a rel=canonical link\"",
            "choices": [
                "parameter stripping",
                "URL cloaking",
                "a 302 redirect",
                "a rel=canonical link"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 51,
            "question": "\"What data vocabulary is most commonly used when marking up content on a page?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"schema.org\"",
            "choices": [
                "vocabulary.org",
                "RDFa.org",
                "schema.org",
                "data-vocabulary.org"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 52,
            "question": "\"According to Google, what type of content includes topics such as news, legal issues, financial advice, and medical information?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"YMYL\"",
            "choices": [
                "RSS",
                "KYC",
                "YMYL",
                "BDB"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 53,
            "question": "\"When would it be necessary to 301 redirect every page on a site?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"when migrating from HTTP to HTTPS\"",
            "choices": [
                "when parameters are used in URLs",
                "when migrating from HTTP to HTTPS",
                "when launching a new redesign",
                "when creating a new subdomain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 54,
            "question": "\"What would contribute to a low bounce rate?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Content reflects search intent.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Content does not match search intent.",
                "Page returns 404 error.",
                "Content reflects search intent.",
                "URL uses parameters."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 55,
            "question": "\"What should be as consistent as possible across the web when developing a local SEO strategy?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"NAP\"",
            "choices": [
                "backlinks",
                "NAP",
                "LRP",
                "inbound links"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 56,
            "question": "\"A user enters a search \\_ to retrieve results from a search engine?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"query\"",
            "choices": [
                "query",
                "parser",
                "bar",
                "link"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 57,
            "question": "\"The search query \"How to make donuts without yeast\" is an example of what?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"long-tail keyword\"",
            "choices": [
                "fresh keyword",
                "operative keyword",
                "short-tail keyword",
                "long-tail keyword"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 58,
            "question": "\"What tool enables companies to display extra information within the natural search results without the need of any structured data?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Google My Business\"",
            "choices": [
                "Google Input Tools",
                "structured data testing tool",
                "Google Tag Manager",
                "Google My Business"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 59,
            "question": "\"Your client is ready to start a blog. but has read that they should put the blog on a subdomain instead of subdirectory in order to create more external links to their website. How would you advise your client about this strategy?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"It is best to have the blog on a subdirectory and build links to primary domain.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Not only should the blog be on a subdomain, but each of the major navigation areas should be on separate subdomains in order to increase the number and value of the links into the primary domain.",
                "It is best to have the blog on a subdirectory and build links to primary domain.",
                "It is an advisable choice as it will enable interlinking between the domains and increase the number of links.",
                "The blog should be on a separate URL to avouud building too many links between the same domain or IP."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 60,
            "question": "\"Blog author pages, each with only one sentence about the author, are at risk of being flagged as **\\_** content.\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"thin\"",
            "choices": [
                "non-indexable",
                "irrelevant",
                "biased",
                "thin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 61,
            "question": "\"What is a common benefit to long-tail keywords?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"They are less competitive, and may have higher conversion rates.\"",
            "choices": [
                "They are less competitive, and may have higher conversion rates.",
                "Long-tail keywords are no longer relevant in today's SEO landscape.",
                "They are less grandular, so you capture broader searches.",
                "They are more competitive, but drive significantly more traffic."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 62,
            "question": "\"You have been asked to help a big e-commerce brand optimize their website for search engines. They currently have thousands of products listed on their website. What is your most appropriate first step?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Conduct a technical audit.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Set campaign goals.",
                "Conduct a technical audit.",
                "Conduct a backlink audit.",
                "Determine keyword strategy."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 63,
            "question": "\"You are optimizing a large e-commerce website. Which strategy will likely yield the most organic traffic?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Optimize each product page with a unique product-specific keyword.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Launch a Smart Shopping Campaign in Google Ads.",
                "Optimize the home page of your website.",
                "Optimize each product page with a unique product-specific keyword.",
                "Optimize your product category pages."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 64,
            "question": "\"Google's Search Quality Evaluator Guidelines describe that experts should write content, especially YMYL content. This is one of the principles seen in the commonly used acronym\\_\\_\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"E-A-T\"",
            "choices": [
                "A.C.E",
                "L-E-A-F",
                "T.R.U.S.T.E.D",
                "E-A-T"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 65,
            "question": "\"Why might using a subdirectory in place of a subdomain be beneficial?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "",
            "choices": [
                "Using a subdirectory is never preferable to using a subdomain.",
                "The subdirectory will allow for keyword dilution.",
                "The subdirectory will benefit from the backlinks the domain has acquired.",
                "The subdirectory is better for the end user experience."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 66,
            "question": "\"What is the best way to provide a search engine with crawl instructions?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Use a robots.txt file.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Use the <crawl> tag.",
                "Use the search engine's Remove URL tool.",
                "Use a robots.txt file.",
                "Use structured data"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 67,
            "question": "\"You are optimizing a site that receives a lot of user-submitted comments, many of which contain a promotional links. According to SEO best practices, how should you treat the comments?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Set links in comments to be Nofollow\"",
            "choices": [
                "Be sure links are using keywork-rich anchor tags",
                "Disallow each link submitted",
                "Set links in comments to be Nofollow",
                "Bold important keywords in comments"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 68,
            "question": "\"What is not a primary component of a SERP snippet?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Cache\"",
            "choices": [
                "Description",
                "Title",
                "Cache",
                "URL"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 69,
            "question": "\"A landing page with no internal or external links is an example of what?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Orphaned content\"",
            "choices": [
                "Dynamic hierarchy",
                "Doorway content",
                "Orphaned content",
                "Flat Hierarchy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 70,
            "question": "\"Informational, navigational, commercial, transactional are four categories of what?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"keyword search intent\"",
            "choices": [
                "keyword search intent",
                "crawling",
                "indexing",
                "HTTP responses"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 71,
            "question": "\"How many H1 tags are typically found on a single page?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"one\"",
            "choices": [
                "up to five",
                "one",
                "as many as necessary",
                "two"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 72,
            "question": "\"What is a meta description used for?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"to summarize the content of a webpage\"",
            "choices": [
                "to summarize the content of a webpage",
                "to bundle meta tags",
                "to describe images",
                "to assign schema markup"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 73,
            "question": "\"Which tool would be best to use to research how many searches per month a term gets?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Google Keyword Planner\"",
            "choices": [
                "Google Search Console",
                "Google Suggest",
                "Google Keyword Planner",
                "Google Tag Manager"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 74,
            "question": "\"What is an example of a top-level domain (TLD)?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\".net\"",
            "choices": [
                ".net",
                "domain.ai",
                "www",
                "301"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 75,
            "question": "\"What does the 301 server response code signify?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Moved Permanently\"",
            "choices": [
                "Not Modified",
                "Moved Permanently",
                "Payment is required",
                "Syntax error in the request"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 76,
            "question": "\"What term is typically used to explain the shuffling of positions in search engine results in between significant updates?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Flux\"",
            "choices": [
                "Flux",
                "Waves",
                "Swaying",
                "Shuffling"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 77,
            "question": "\"Which of the following declarations about FFA web pages are true?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"They are also called link farms.\"",
            "choices": [
                "They are paid listings.",
                "They are also called link farms.",
                "They are significantly beneficial to search engine optimization.",
                "They contain various inbound links."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 78,
            "question": "\"What is the generally approved distinction in between SEO and also SEM?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Search engine optimization focuses on organic/natural search positions, sem encompasses all facets of search marketing.\"",
            "choices": [
                "SEO refers to organic/natural listings while sem covers pay per click, or paid search.",
                "Search engine optimization focuses on organic/natural search positions, sem encompasses all facets of search marketing.",
                "No difference, they're synonymous.",
                "SEO has a tendency to be a west shore term, sem is much more eastern shore."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 79,
            "question": "\"Which of the following link building techniques do online search engine tacitly recommend?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Viral content creation & promotion.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Reciprocal link exchange programs.",
                "Viral content creation & promotion.",
                "Renting out pages from trustworthy domains and also positioning web links on them.",
                "Purchasing web links from web link brokers & networks."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 80,
            "question": "\"What is the full form of SEO?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Search Engine Optimization.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Search Engine Optimum.",
                "Search Engine Optimization.",
                "Search Electronic Optimization.",
                "None of the above."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 81,
            "question": "\"Which of the following is the process of fetching all the web pages connected to a web site?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Crawling\"",
            "choices": [
                "Indexing",
                "Crawling",
                "Processing",
                "All of the Above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 82,
            "question": "\"What does the 302 server response code signify?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"The web page has actually temporarily moved.\"",
            "choices": [
                "It symbolizes dispute, way too many individuals desired the exact same documents at the same time.",
                "The web page has actually been permanently removed.",
                "The technique you are making use of to access the file is not allowed.",
                "The web page has actually temporarily moved.",
                "What you requested is just also large to process."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 83,
            "question": "\"Which of the following declarations about RSS are proper?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"It is a form of XML.\"",
            "choices": [
                "It is a form of XML.",
                "It stands for Realtime streamlined syndication.",
                "It is an excellent way of presenting static information.",
                "It is a microsoft technology."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 84,
            "question": "\"Which of the following search engines or directories supplies the major search results for AOL?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Google\"",
            "choices": [
                "Lycos",
                "DMOZ",
                "Google",
                "Yahoo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 85,
            "question": "\"Google gives priority to themed in-bound links.\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"True\"",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 86,
            "question": "\"Which of the following methods can help you get around the Google Sandbox?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Buying an old Website as well as getting it ranked.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Buying an old Website as well as getting it ranked.",
                "Buying a Google Adwords PPC campaign.",
                "Placing the website on a sub domain of a ranked site and afterwards 301 re-directing the site after it has actually been indexed.",
                "Getting a DMOZ listing."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 87,
            "question": "\"Google looks down upon paid links for enhancing page ranking. If a web site sells web links, what action/s does Google suggest to avoid being penalized?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Paid links need to be divulged via the \"rel= nofollow\" attribute in the hyperlink.\"",
            "choices": [
                "The text of the paid links should state words \"paid text link\" for Google to recognize it as a paid web link.",
                "Only Paid text web links to non profit websites should be accepted.",
                "Paid links need to be divulged via the \"rel= nofollow\" attribute in the hyperlink.",
                "Paid links ought to be disclosed through the \"index= nofollow\" attribute in the hyperlink."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 88,
            "question": "\"What will take place if you type the word 'Certification-Python' in the Google search box?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Google will locate ALL the web pages in which the words \"Certification\" and \"Python\" appear together.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Google will certainly locate the web pages about \"certification\" and additionally consisting of the word \"python\".",
                "Google will certainly locate ALL the web pages having the word \"Certification\" and \"Python\".",
                "Google will locate ALL the web pages in which the words \"Certification\" and \"Python\" appear together.",
                "Google will find the web pages about Certification that do not consist of the word Python."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 89,
            "question": "\"What is keyword density?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"The number of times the keyword is used/ the total word count on the web page.\"",
            "choices": [
                "The number of times the keyword is utilized/ (separated by) the total word count on page-- (minus) the complete words in HTML on the page.",
                "The variety of times the keyword is used x (multiply by) the total word count on web page.",
                "The number of times the keyword is utilized in the page description.",
                "The number of times the search phrase is used in the web page title.",
                "The number of times the keyword is used/ the total word count on the web page."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 90,
            "question": "\"Which of the following statement about FFA web pages hold true?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"They are additionally called Link Farms.\"",
            "choices": [
                "They are significantly beneficial to SEO.",
                "They are additionally called Link Farms.",
                "They are Paid Listings.",
                "They contain various incoming links."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 91,
            "question": "\"What elements of a hyperlink are not important for SEO?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"The exposure of the link text.\"",
            "choices": [
                "The exposure of the link text.",
                "The anchor text, particularly the keywords in it.",
                "The area from which the web link stems.",
                "The location to which the link leads."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 92,
            "question": "\"Which of the technique is NOT an \"ideal practice\" for developing excellent quality title tags?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Limit the tag to 65 characters, including spaces\"",
            "choices": [
                "Make sure the title is unique for every page",
                "Include an exhaustive list of keywords",
                "Limit the tag to 65 characters, including spaces",
                "Write compelling copy that encourages users to \u201cclick\u201d your listing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 93,
            "question": "\"Which HTTP web server reaction code suggests a file that no more exists? (File Not Found).\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"404\"",
            "choices": [
                "40A",
                "30A",
                "500",
                "404"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 94,
            "question": "\"What is Page Rank?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"The method Google measures exactly how popular a provided page is based upon the number and also quality of sites that connect to it.\"",
            "choices": [
                "The Alexa modern technology for ranking web pages.",
                "The means Yahoo! actions just how popular an offered web page is based on the number as well as quality of websites that connect to it.",
                "The search significance of a web page contrasted to the other web pages in the online search engine.",
                "The method Google measures exactly how popular a provided page is based upon the number and also quality of sites that connect to it."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 95,
            "question": "\"Your sitemap shows this entry: <lastmod>2020-09-09T19:34:00+01:00</lastmod>. What does +01:00 refer to?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"time zone designator\"",
            "choices": [
                "time between publishing and updating",
                "time since last sitemap crawl",
                "time zone designator",
                "suggested content priority"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 96,
            "question": "\"What markup language is most commonly used for sitemaps?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"XML\"",
            "choices": [
                "RSS",
                "XLS",
                "Javascript",
                "XML"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 97,
            "question": "\"What markup language is most commonly used for sitemaps?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"XML\"",
            "choices": [
                "RSS",
                "XLS",
                "Javascript",
                "XML"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 98,
            "question": "\"You are searching for a website that was published within last week. When you type in the URL, the site does not appear in Google search results. Why might this be?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"The site is not in Google's index\"",
            "choices": [
                "You are searching on desktop and must wait for mobile-first indexing",
                "The site is not in Google's index",
                "The website needs backling to be discovered by Googlebot",
                "The website does not have a high enough domain authority"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 99,
            "question": "\"In which scenario is using a 301 redirect preferred over a canonical link?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"when treating uppercase versus lowercase characters in URLs\"",
            "choices": [
                "When using faceted navigation",
                "when treating uppercase versus lowercase characters in URLs",
                "with an on-site search results page",
                "when managing URL parameters"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 100,
            "question": "\"What would be most beneficial in helping a site display rich features in Google's search results?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"structured data\"",
            "choices": [
                "Google search console",
                "structured data",
                "Data-Vocabulary.org",
                "Google Result Generator"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 101,
            "question": "\"Which statement is true regarding the use of social signals, such as LinkedIn shares, by Google in its ranking algorithm?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "",
            "choices": [
                "Social signals provide a benefit only if they have structured data markup",
                "Social signals are identical to backlinks",
                "Google does not use social signals to determine rank"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 102,
            "question": "\"How many outbound links should you include in each blog posting?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "",
            "choices": [
                "at least 2",
                "at least five",
                "at least seven",
                "as many as are relevent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "Search Engine Optimization (SEO)",
            "id": 103,
            "question": "\"What tag should you use to signal the main topic heading of a page?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`<h1>`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`<h1>`",
                "`<h0>`",
                "`<strong>`",
                "`<em>`"
            ]
        }
    ]
}